William Langner Papers
William Langner Papers
- Printed material, in Hollinger cartons, very heavy
  - Misc journals (Box 147)
  - Misc newsletters
    - Partial list of titles (Box 148)
    - Newsletters, A-E, includes "ABE Newsletter" (Virginia Department of Education), "Adult and Continuing Education Today" (Washington DC) (Box 148)
    - Newsletters, F-Net, includes "GED Briefs," "GED Items" and "GED Profiles" (American Council on Education), "Lifeline" (Florida Adult Literacy Resource Center) (Box 149)
    - Newsletters, New-W, includes "What's the Buzz?" (Pennsylvania ABE), "Written Word" (American Association of Advertising Agencies) (Box 150)
  - Miscellaneous education material, 7 boxes - 6 Hollinger, 1ab (Box 151-157)
- Writings
  - Published material
    - Adult learning activities (Box 158)
    - Adult learning seminars (Box 158)
  - Manuscripts
    - Adult education materials, co-written with Bonnie Dedeian, Charlie Schmidt, notes, contracts, correspondence, drafts, research material for GED preparatory books; 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Brand talking points (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous, A-Ev, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous, Ex-U, 4 folders (Box 159)
    - Miscellaneous untitled (Box 159)
  - Notebooks (Box 159)
  - Outlines, fragments, notes, 2 folders (Box 160)
  - Miscellaneous, notes, reminders, to-do lists, other scraps and fragments; 5 folders (Box 160, 161)